Can I help you?
我能帮你做什么吗?
Yes,please.We reserved some rooms.
Yes,please. 我们预定了些房间.
What's the name?
什么名字?
We're with the International Summer Basketball League.
我们是国际夏日篮球联盟.
Oh yes.
We prefer rooms high up.
我们想住高层.
Of course.
没问题.
Away from traffic,and with nice views.
远离交通喧哗, 和好的视野.
I think you'll be pleased with these.
我想您会对这些满意的.
-You've reserved six double rooms. -Yes.
-您预定了六个双人房. -Yes.
-With bath. -Yes.
-带洗澡间的. -Yes.
-And twin beds? -Yes.
-双人床? -Yes.
-And one single room. -Yes.
-一个单人房. -Yes.
With bath.
带洗澡间的.
Yes.And a king-size bed.
Yes. 特大号床.
That's right.
Good.
Is breakfast included?
早餐包括在里面吗?
I'm afraid not.
恐怕不包括.
Ah well.
Ah 好吧.
Here is a list of our breakfast requirements.
这张列表是我们对早餐的要求.
Please warn the kitchen.Thank you.Good day.
请提醒厨房. 谢谢你 .再见.
Jarmusch? We have to talk.
Jarmusch? 我们得谈谈.